[Music]
hey what is up guys I'm to be HD here
and welcome to what's on my phone
20:19 see I've done this sort of thing
roughly once a year and it always tends
to be kind of the same as the last year
but this year I'm gonna put a little bit
more of the other devices that I use so
it's more of a look at the ecosystem of
things that I use somewhat daily right
now and this is right at that like
perfect time of the year where we're in
the lull after the holiday season where
I can sort of settle into one device for
more than a month at a time we're about
to start to get new phones again but for
the moment this is what I've chosen to
settle into so you probably noticed I
have two phones in front of me I'm gonna
go through them both I'm gonna start
with my Android phone but I do carry an
Android phone of choice and an iPhone of
choice as you know those phones are
pixel three XL and iPhone 10s max black
Space Gray all right so this is my
probably pretty familiar looking pixel
set up at this point
like I've said not a ton changing but
I'll go through the the icons on widgets
anyway I'll leave the wallpaper link
below of course but a tick tick that's
my to-do list app I don't think I'd be
nearly as productive without actually
writing things down as when I actually
write them down like if you asked me to
do something and I don't write it down
and I tell you I'm gonna do it I'm not
gonna do it I actually have to write it
down but then I have Google keep which I
see they've called keep notes now but
it's just to keep lists of things and to
remember what's upcoming then there's
Instagram I think we all know what
Instagram is and then there's Google
photos over here which is a stock Photos
app for the pixel then pocket casts and
this is something I've gotten more into
lately but I've started listening to
more podcasts from various creators
there's podcast networks there's news
sites and all sorts of people do
podcasts now NBA players even so I use
the pot pocket cast app to sort through
those download them listen to them on
flights and car rides and things like
that I use relay Pro still for reddit I
use a different reddit app on the iPhone
but I'll get into that later relay Pro
is great that's the Tesla app I haven't
had my car for at this point almost
three months
and there's an update on that coming
very soon but I still have the test lap
lonely hasn't been opened in a while on
my phone then there's Spotify that's
just all the music I listen to a lot of
music still in the car or whether I'm
working out or whatever I'm doing and I
have actually added an mkbhd
videos playlist and all i've started
linking that below as well so the video
intro music you hear in a lot of videos
you can find it on spotify and so i've
started adding them to this playlist so
shadow to spotify so in the last two on
this row youtube studio app pretty a
pretty standard stuff i think you've all
seen that before and Google Maps I'd be
lost without it but I use Waze which is
on my next page at the bottom I always
have my txt app and a dialer I have my
camera always over there and part of the
reason I've been using the pixel for for
all this time
especially over my second-favorite phone
right now in the Android world which is
the one plus 60 is the camera the one
plus is a better performer it is
significantly faster smoother doesn't
take up nearly as much has way more RAM
it's just more pleasurable to use but
the camera is not as good and every time
I come back and take photos on this
pixels camera it reminds me why I really
liked it in the first place so that's
gonna be something really difficult for
other phones to top in the future but
pixels camera is what's keeping me here
then I have the Play Store and I also
have my Twitter app of choice on Android
it's called flamingo it's no longer
available for additional users in the
Play Store so it's it's kind of a
useless shout-out but it's one of my
favorite Twitter apps of all time but I
don't get notifications through it I use
the official Twitter app for
notifications so that's my sort of weird
twitter situation and I'll scroll over
there's my calendar app I forgot the
name of it but it's really good so I'll
link it below and it just lets you click
on calendar from up top and then there's
ways this is what I use for navigation
so it'll tell you if there's potholes on
the road ahead
or if there's anything like closed roads
or construction traffic is really really
good with Waze so I recommend ways then
there's Java fantasy
I recently dethroned the best team in
our league but I'm only 11 and 5 in the
16 weeks of the NBA season so I'm not
I'm not on top yet shout-out to Jesse
and I think that's uh that's Mike so
good job candy then I
My Fitness Pal which is an app basically
used to track macros and fitness and
calories and things like that then
SoundCloud my second favorite music app
stuff that's not on Spotify which is
very little I can listen to on
soundcloud and then group me for all the
group chat action but of course like any
other Android phone there are plenty of
apps that are not on my homescreen that
are still on my phone AccuWeather is
just a great weather app I think most
people know what that does after ship is
pretty good for just letting you know
what happened with your packages whether
they've arrived yet you can see the
titanium red hydrogen's that I ordered
are on the way so Android auto audible
audible is good for audio books I've
read at least three books in the last
year so that's pretty good breather
haven't used that in awhile but I've
talked about it before let's you rent
space in your area if you live in a city
where there's a lot of breathers and
calculator Calendar camera chrome clock
coinbase remember Bitcoin good times
dark sky dark skies are really good
hyper local weather app so it's sort of
crowd-sourced and wow that's a lot of
rain or something coming awesome but
it's a hyperlocal weather app and it can
give you notifications about if it's
gonna rain in the next couple of minutes
it'll say hey it's gonna start drizzling
in 17 minutes and raining hard in 24 I
know exactly how long you have to get
out of wherever you're at so I like dark
sky Google Fitness I don't use as much
you may notice I wear an Apple watch and
I've developed this obsession with
closing my rings it's what a lot of
people with Apple watches end up doing
it's telling me to breathe right now
headphones this is the Sony headphones
app so you guys saw that I reviewed the
Sony WH 1000 X and threes pretty
recently that was with minimal
experience with the app and there's a
couple cool features in the app where
you can customize what it does but
that's the app on my phone now then
there's a health main - a digital scale
that I have literally tells me mostly
just how much I weigh but you guys
didn't know how much I weighed so
there's your your insight into that
hashtag gains philips hue there's a
couple philips hue lights in here
including that one behind my desk that's
been there for years now
gotta love philips you stuff i also have
the lifx app because i've been
experimenting experimenting with those
they talked to Google home as well and
that
have to go through all these LD is
called lens distortions so you can open
up a photo in the lens distortions app
and then there's a whole bunch of
different effects and built-in that you
can play with to adjust how the photo
looks adds essentially overlay so you
can adjust opacity intensity oven
filters it's pretty cool I don't use it
that much but it is useful at what it
does and I also have Lightroom mobile
that I use even less often than the
actual built-in photo editor in Google
Photos but it is good for certain things
as well then there's the me Ross app
that's an app that I got specifically
for a smart plug that needed to use that
app to talk to it but then it could turn
on and off a holiday tree for the past
year so it worked as nest there's
Pandora I only have two different
wallpaper apps that I use regularly
one of them's papers and it's very
similar to the other one I use which is
called wall-e down here at the bottom
Wal Li I'm also gonna try to link as
many of these apps as possible down
below so the description is gonna be
really long but ideally you can find
everything there then we're getting down
to the end I have a photo blend app I
have pocket casts I have the regular
reddit app that's good for notifications
I have slack I have Ries plash what is
Ries pleasue
oh it's more it's more wallpapers I
forgot I had a third one I don't use
this one as much I have the stock X app
this one can be a bit of a problem
because if you're into shoes or street
wear but for me mostly just shoes then
you can just kind of endlessly graze
through here and find things that you
want highly recommended and then you get
to the bottom on those YouTube YouTube
TV YouTube music YouTube studio and
Zillow for just perusing real estate and
that's basically it so that's that's the
apps that are on my Android phone again
I don't use all these apps all the time
the ones that are mainly on my home
screen are the ones that I most often
use like with most people but I also
have an iPhone and that's where all I'll
do a lot of stuff that's just works
better on the iPhone so I'll link again
this wallpaper for my iPhone below but
again just a bunch of apps that are good
on the iPhone that aren't necessarily as
good on Android so things like snapchat
Instagram for Instagram stories and then
there's a bunch of duplicates just
because sometimes I find myself using
the iPhone
more so the camera there's Google photos
at the top for backing up your photos
there is the actual Photos app and then
there's the calendar which is good for
just telling me the date I don't
actually use the calendar app on the
iPhone it's completely blank
but the icon shows the date and that's
why I keep it there there's the wallet
the wallet apps on Android are all
really finicky and a little I would say
untrustworthy fun fact if you go to an
Apple event they will actually put a
pass in your wallet app that they will
scan and let you in with so they just
kind of expect you to use their products
so I have the wallet app and Spotify on
SoundCloud right next to each other the
app store settings
YouTube YouTube studio pocket casts a
lot of duplicates as you can see a lot
of competitors next to each other as
well and then I have Instagram and my
tik tik app which does sync with the tik
tik app on my iPad on my Android phone
and everything else
I love multi-platform sync and then in
my dock people thought I was trolling
when I put these here but I have the the
dialer I have the messages app Safari
and the Google app and this is gonna
give me the same Google cards that are
on my Android phone a little bit slower
not as real-time but I can still trigger
Google assistant from here I can still
open google lens and identify things
from the camera it still does all that
same stuff then of course on the second
page any iPhone user knows you just have
folders of junk that you don't open that
much and since you can't move them or
hide them anywhere to a drawer my
folders are junk are the Apple folder
the utilities folder I have three games
because I don't really game that much on
my phones but I have osmose ass well
nine and Colour road and I have a Google
app which has some Google apps in it or
Google folder so that's my my junk
folders at the top pocket Dropbox dark
sky again venmo again sky guide in my
opinion sky guide is the best AR app
period I'm just gonna toss that out
there if you open sky guide daytime or
night and point it up the sky it will
show you in real time where
constellations are our celestial objects
are where the Sun the Moon the planets
and everything is and it overlays it
with your actual environment the trees
the buildings the skyline it's really
cool highly recommended then the
activity app which again if you're ever
concerned about closing
there's your history of rings being
closed or sometimes not closed but don't
pay too much attention to that and then
on the last page I actually use these
more than the middle page so the series
shortcuts app the Snapseed app for photo
editing uber swing-u is a golf app so
for those of you who play golf
there's a bunch of apps that do this but
literally it connects to GPS and as you
walk around the golf course it'll tell
you exactly how far you are from the
hole from whatever hazards you're near
things like that it's pretty smart then
there's IG TV yeah I remember that
then there's the Hasselblad focus app in
theory it would be the perfect way to
transfer photos from the Hasselblad x1d
that i use to my iphone and then edit
them on the iphone unfortunately it's
very very picky and usually when I want
to use it it's a crowded Wi-Fi network
and it's it's hard to switch it over so
it could be a lot better I don't use it
much but I want to use it more the low
metric time app for that clock I
reviewed a long time ago and then there
is the xej app which is the one
wallpaper app that I use on the iPhone
so my iPad my beloved iPad pro I've
found every excuse to use this over a
MacBook Pro for example for the past
couple weeks
like I've said in these videos I kind of
gave it a rave review here's what's on
my iPad pro so a lot of the same stuff
that's been on my iPhone is duplicated
so I'm not gonna say that stuff again
aside from the fact that yes I have the
calendar up there just cuz it shows a
date but really I just have three pages
of apps I don't even have that many
trash folders on here because I use a
lot of the stuff on the iPad first
couple rows I have that Apple folder
just to have a bunch of junk in it
Spotify on SoundCloud next to each other
Lightroom ticktick but some of the first
true iPad apps that I have our games
golf battle which is it's so stupid it's
literally just a just a putt-putt game
it's a mini mini golf but like with your
hand it's one of those super simple
addicting games and then earn to die
which is a game I've played on Android
but it's sort of like a horizontal
scroller similar to Mario but you're
driving a cart with weapons on it and
zombies are sort of attacking you that
that type of thing and then Osmos HD
this is another one
games that just looks amazing on a
tablet and even if it's not the most
action-packed thing the concept of it
I'll leave like I said links to these
below but you play through it and it's
beautiful there's a great soundtrack you
got headphones on you can get really
immersed in this game so I'll recommend
Osmos HD and then just a bunch of apps
that I use to to get work done on the
iPad Google keep Google Drive Google
Docs not even that crazy professional
apps I'm not doing any video editing on
here but I do have live library mcc on
here because I can do photo editing and
then X rollover and there's some real
tier apps so how's for interior design
realtor.com I also have Zillow on here I
have a weather app I found this app
called medley that kind of lets you
attempt to make music I'm not very good
at it so I don't claim to be an expert
at that at all but it's super fun
Netflix I haven't really used Netflix
very much over the years
I made an account a long time ago never
really used it but as I've been going on
a lot of flights lately I found I've
wanted to watch stuff podcasts don't
really last six whole hours usually so
there's some good stuff that I
downloaded Netflix has been a good
source for that I usually try to use my
iPad for as much mobile work as possible
I still hate typing on the iPad here's
the thing about the iPad this is the
keyboard and you can't really quite know
so you have huge hands reach the middle
of the iPad pro keyboard especially if
it's landscape but the iPad pro is the
only iPad where you can't split the
keyboard so I guess on the smaller iPads
you can do this little gesture and then
a Swiss to the size and you can type
like this but on an iPad pro it won't do
that so you end up being this hunt peck
type type of person I don't know why so
I do most things like email or things
that require a lot of typing to reply
out to stuff or writing out like video
ideas I do that on my laptop because I
have a real keyboard and I can actually
type but I will not be mad if I find
myself stuck with just an iPad pro and
then I just have to die like weirdly
with my thumbs
in that annoying way I'll get it done
anyway that's my iPad alright last but
not least the desktop iMac pro 2019
fully maxed out this is where the the
editing and
the production and the magic happens I
guess you could say but it's also my
daily machine so I'll go through the
apps and things on this so usually it's
either in the launchpad all the stuff in
here or the doc a lot of people used to
do what's on my doc videos the HOS good
times they used to be a lot of a lot of
people doing what's on my doc videos so
here's what's in my doc finder tick tick
my to-do list app that's high-lift then
there's Final Cut Pro the editing suite
of choice Safari which is now my default
web browser I do also have Chrome but I
do use Safari for the most part on the
Mac to Spotify for the desktop tweet bot
for all that Twitter goodness the App
Store of course System Preferences and
the control panel for the Apollo twin
that I currently use for my audio setup
and I keep my desktop pretty clean
there's usually not a whole lot of spare
extra icons going on I usually usually
have just the web browser and Twitter up
I really really miss the dual screen
setup of the past back in those days in
2013 and 20 2012 I guess those are the
days when I most often used a dual
screen setup and I'm really excited for
the the modular Mac this year so I can
use whatever monitor I want I can go
back to having to but for now for the
most part it's the iMac so it's just one
monitor you can see the 80 terabyte rate
of attached storage up here that's the
promise Pegasus over here that shows up
because it's a mounted hard drive and
that's where I have a whole bunch of
footage from previous videos and from
current projects but also down here you
can see the jellyfish as well doesn't
show up as a mount to drive but over
there back behind me that's a hundred
and twenty terabytes of hard drives and
that's the current server that's our
network attack store network network
attached storage the weird if it was a
tax storage but it's attached storage
but anyway that shows up as an initial
location it's called jellyfish there's
all the same and could be HD stuff and
we have current video projects and I
won't click in there because there's
some top-secret stuff but you'll see
that very soon but that's what we use to
have multiple people working on the same
Final Cut Pro project at the same time
really impressive stuff it's called the
luma 4 jellyfish at least that's what
the hardware's called
and I've loved that so far for like the
past couple weeks but yeah this is this
is the hub this is obviously where
everything has to render this is where
things get uploaded and published and
it's been a workhorse so far you can go
back and watch the iMac Pro review if
you have any other questions about that
but that's basically it honestly that's
just uh it's just a lot of what you've
seen before and a bunch of other various
places but all in one video if you have
any other questions I'll hang out in the
comment section below and talk through
whether it's workflow questions or app
questions or if I forgot a wallpaper or
some link you need me to drop below I'll
keep doing that but that's basically it
thanks for watching catch you guys in
the next one peace